â¬…ï¸ Left Arrow\*ï¸âƒ£ Asteriskâ­ StarOption Slidersâœ‰ï¸ MailExit

Dazed media sites

Share

[](javascript:void((function()%7Bvar%20e=document.createElement('script');e.setAttribute('type','text/javascript');e.setAttribute('charset','UTF-8');e.setAttribute('src','https://assets.pinterest.com/js/pinmarklet.js?r='+Math.random()*99999999);document.body.appendChild(e)%7D)()); "Pinterest")

Privacy Policy
==============

This policy explains how Dazed Digital uses personal information which we collect from you
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

August 102008

Text[Dazed Digital](https://www.dazeddigital.com/user/dazeddigital)

### **Dazed & Confused – Privacy Notice**

Dazed Group Limited (us, or we) are the data controller in respect of your personal information. This  
privacy notice sets out the basis on which any of your personal information we collect from you or third  
parties, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.

Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal information and  
how it will be treated.

### **1\. How and when we collect personal information about you**

1.1 We collect and process personal information when you:  
1.1.1 visit our website, www.dazeddigital.com, (including when leaving any reviews or comments, or filling in forms on our site, such as when you sign up for newsletters or enter a competition or participate in a campaign or project, including with our collaborative competitions/projects in partnership with various brands);  
1.1.2 \[purchase any products from our website or subscribe to any of our services, including digital subscriptions\];  
1.1.3 register to and/or attend our events;  
1.1.4 contact our customer service centres or request information from us in any other way;  
1.1.5 participate in our customer satisfaction surveys or other market research; and  
1.1.6 communicate with us via social networking websites, third party apps or similar technologies.  
1.2 We will indicate where any personal information we have requested is mandatory or optional. We will also explain the consequences should you decide not to provide information which we have indicated is mandatory. In some circumstances this may mean we are unable to provide you with a certain service or product.  
1.3 We may also collect information about you from third party sources, such as from related third parties such as sub-contractors.

### **2\. What personal information do we collect about you**

2.1 We may collect and process the following personal information about you:

**2.1.1 Submitted Information**

We may collect and process the following personal information about you which you  
provide to us:

(a) contact details (such as your name, address, email address and telephone  
number);  
(b) demographic information (such as age and/or other information that may identify you as an individual);  
(c) responses to any customer satisfaction surveys or market research (unless these are provided anonymously);(d) financial and credit card information if you purchase products/subscriptions from us;  
(e) your marketing preferences; and  
(f) any other information which you choose to provide to us via the website or otherwise.

**2.1.2 Additional information**

(a) \[We will collect and store you purchase history with us.\] We will also collect data regarding your attendance at our events or participation in competitions or brand/partnership campaigns.  
(b) If you contact us with a complaint or query, we may keep a record of any phone number used to call our customer service number as well as the correspondence and the period of time it took for us to deal with a query or any request you had. We may also record your levels of satisfaction with the services we have provided.  
(c) At some of our events, we may photograph, record or film onsite activities and CCTV may be in operation at some locations. In which case, you may be filmed, photographed or recorded as part of any such activities. We endeavour to provide clear notices of any photography or footage being taken at events.  
(d) When you visit our website and other digital properties, we may also collect information from you automatically, for example using cookies and other similar technologies. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we may set on your device. This type of information may include the following:  
(i) information about your device, operating system and IP address;  
(ii) your login information;  
(iii) browser type and version; and  
(iv) information about your visit, including URL, clickstream (i.e. your journey to, through and from our site), length of visits to certain pages, and page interaction information.

2.2 You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them in the [Cookies section](https://www.dazeddigital.com/cookie-policy) of our Website [Terms of Use](https://www.dazeddigital.com/info/article/825/1/terms-conditions) and you can manage how they are used by use and our partners by visiting the Privacy Settings

### **3\. Purposes for processing your personal information**

3.1 We may process your personal information for the following purposes:  
3.1.1 to provide you with the information, products and services you have requested and send you marketing and advertising materials;  
3.1.2 to authenticate your access to our website and other digital properties;  
3.1.3 for system administration purposes and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;  
3.1.4 to monitor your use of our website and other digital properties to improve the user experience and to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device;  
3.1.5 to provide user support and ensure we provide a good level of customer service;  
3.1.6 to tailor any marketing or advertising so that it is more relevant to you;  
3.1.7 to notify you of any changes to our services;  
3.1.8 to conduct marketing analysis to allow us to assess trends and the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing campaigns (including using your personal information to evaluate, analyse or predict certain personal aspects relating to you, such as your preferences, economic situation, interests, and/or location);  
3.1.9 if you are filmed, photographed or recorded as part of any onsite activities at one of our events, your image or likeness may be used in promotional material, sponsor, exhibitor and media partner coverage in print, online and on broadcast television;  
3.1.10 for security and fraud prevention;  
3.1.11 to ensure that our website and digital properties are safe and secure; and  
3.1.12 to comply with applicable laws and regulations.  
3.2 We may also match personal information that you provide to us directly with other information about you obtained from or held by third party sources (such as social media platforms). This may include your contact details, demographic data, your social media interactions, preferences, interests, geographic location and age or age range. We may use this personal information to tailor and show advertisements more relevant to you either on our website or on third party websites (including social media platforms).

### **4\. Legal basis for processing your personal information**

We will only process your personal information where we have a legal basis to do so. The legal basis will depend on the purposes for which we have collected and use your personal information. In almost every case the legal basis will be one of the following:

(a) Consent: For example, where you have provided your consent to receive certain marketing from us. You can withdraw your consent at any time, including by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any marketing email we send you.  
(b) Our legitimate business interests: Where it is necessary for us to understand our users, promote our services and operate effectively as a style and culture magazine and digital platform provided in each case that this is done in a legitimate way which does not unduly affect your privacy and other rights. For example, we will rely on this legal basis when we conduct certain market analysis to understand our users in sufficient detail, so we can create new services and improve the profile of our brand.  
(c) Performance of a contract with you (or in order to take steps prior to entering into a contract with you): For example, where you have purchased a product from us and we need to use your contact details and payment information in order to process your order and send the product to you.  
(d) Compliance with law: Where we are subject to a legal obligation and need to use your personal information in order to comply with that obligation.

### **5\. Where we store your personal information**

5.1 The personal information that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the UK or the European Economic Area (the EEA), including countries, which have less strict, or no data protection laws, when compared to those in the UK and Europe.  
5.2 Whenever we transfer your information as described in the paragraph above, we will take steps which are reasonably necessary to ensure that adequate safeguards are in place to protect your personal information and to make sure it is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy notice. In these cases, we rely on approved data transfer mechanisms (such as the EU “Standard Contractual Clauses” and the EU-US “Privacy Shield”) to ensure your information is subject to adequate safeguards in the recipient country. If you are located in the UK or the EEA, you may contact us for a copy of the safeguards which we have put in place to protect your personal information and privacy rights in these circumstances.

### **6\. How we keep your personal information**

6.1 We take steps to ensure that the personal information that you provide is retained for only as long as it is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected. After this period it will be deleted or in some cases anonymised. For example, where you have made a purchase with us, we will keep a record of your purchase for the period necessary for invoicing, tax and warranty purposes. We may also keep a record of correspondence with you (for example if you have made a complaint) for as long as is necessary to protect us from a legal claim.  
6.2 Where we have collected the personal information based on your consent and we have no other lawful basis to continue with that processing, if you subsequently withdraw your consent then we will delete your personal information. However, please note that where you unsubscribe from our marketing communications, we will keep a record of your email address to ensure we do not send you marketing emails in future.

### **7\. Children**

Our website and other digital properties are not intended for, and should not be used by, children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under 13.

### **8\. Disclosing your information**

8.1 We may share your personal information within our group of companies (i.e. our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006).  
8.2 We may share your personal information with our suppliers, business partners and service providers, where they are helping us to market and advertise our services as well as providing our services to you.  
8.3 We will share your personal information with any selected third party that you consent to our sharing your information with for marketing purposes, for example any brand partners we collaborate with in connection with campaigns or competitions. We will always ask for your consent to do so before sharing with any such parties.  
8.4 We may disclose your personal information to other third parties in the following cases:  
8.4.1 for the purposes of research, evaluation, and analysis;  
8.4.2 in the event that we sell any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective buyer of such business or assets  
8.4.3 if we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by us about our customers and visitors to our websites will be one of the transferred assets;  
8.4.4 if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal or regulatory obligation or request; or  
8.4.5 to protect the rights, property or safety of us or our users, or others, and in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions (this includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction).

### **9\. Your rights to the information we hold about you**

9.1 You have certain rights in relation to your personal information. These include: the right to be informed of the ways in which we use your information (as we seek to do in this Privacy Notice), the right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes (such as marketing purposes), the right to access your personal information, the right to request that we correct or rectify any information that we hold about you which is out of date or incorrect, to restrict or erase your information (in certain circumstances), or to receive a machine-readable copy of your personal information.  
9.2 We will handle any request to exercise your rights in accordance with applicable law and any relevant legal exemptions. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us using the contact details below.  
9.3 You may also have the right to complain to a data protection authority such as the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (https://ico.org.uk/) (or relevant authority in your country of residence) if you think we have processed your personal information in a manner which is unlawful or breaches your rights. If you have such concerns we request that you initially contact us (using the contact details below) so that we can investigate, and hopefully resolve, your concerns.  
9.4 Our website and other digital properties may, from time to time, contain links to and from third party websites and services such as our business partners and advertisers. If you follow a link to any of these websites and/or services, please note that they have their own privacy notices and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for them. Please check any such third party privacy notices before you submit any personal information to these websites or services.

### **10\. Changes to this privacy notice**

We may change this privacy notice at any time. The new privacy notice will be displayed on our website and in the applicable digital property. The date this privacy noticed was last updated appears at the bottom.

### **11\. Contact us**

11.1 Questions and comments regarding this privacy notice should be sent to: [matt.baskerville@dazedmedia.com](mailto:matt.baskerville@dazedmedia.com).  
11.2 Our registered offices are located at Second Floor, 2 Arundel Street, London, England, WC2R 3DA.

**This Privacy Notice was last updated on 27 April 2020**
